Finding Aid for the Ronald Jacobs Papers PASC.0355
UCLA Library Special Collections
- That Girl
  - That Shoplifter - revised script, 1970 Oct 23 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - There Sure Are a Bunch of Cards in St. Louis (Part One) - revised script, 1970 Aug 7 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - There Sure Are a Bunch of Cards in St. Louis (Part Two) - revised script, 1970 Aug 14 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - There's No Business - script, 1969 Jun 5 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Writers: Johnson, Coslough
  - There's No Business - script (2 copies), 1969 Nov 24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - These Boots Weren't Made for Walking - revised script, 1966 Oct 26 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - They Shoot Pictures, Don't They? - revised script, 1970 Jan 10 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - This Little Piggy Had a Ball - revised script, 1967 Feb 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Writers: Margolin, Arnold; Parker, Jim
  - Time for Arrest - revised script, 1966 Sep 16 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Two for the Money - revised script, 1970 Sep 25 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Writers: Nicholas, San
  - Ugh Wilderness - revised script, 1969 Oct 31 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Uncle Herbert for All Seasons (An) - revised script, 1970 Jul 31 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Writers: Garland, Bob
  - What Are Your Intentions? - script, 1966 Dec 29 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - What's In a Name - revised script, 1966 Sep 9 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Formerly titled Pilot Show.
  - Will You Marry Me? - script, 1970 Mar 27 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Women, Awake, Women, Arise - script, 1970 Apr 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Women's Lib - script, 1970 Nov 11 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - You Have to Know Someone to be an Unknown - revised script, 1967 Jan 20 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Formerly titled Who Was That Lady?
  - You Told It Right How Could You? - scripts (2 copies), 1969 Sep 15 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Writers: Flippen, R. B.
- Accession PASC-0355-2012-12 backlog material, PASC-0355-2012-12 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)